Yune-san, you look erotic.
ユネさん、エロい格好してるね
I was made to wear it.
着させられちゃったんだ
Keep your hair in front.
髪前にしてて
Have you ever worn something like this?
こんな履いたことある?
do not have.
ない
Have you never been here?
来たことないの?
Open your legs.
足開いて
more.
もっと
So, stick it out.
で、突き出して
Kuro-chan, take these pants.
クロちゃん、これパンツ持って
Assemble it.
組み上げて
Hey, go to bed.
おまえ、ベッド行って
Move your pussy.
自分のおまんこずらして
Move it to your breasts.
おっぱいにずらして
It feels right.
しっくりして
Kuro-chan, be careful of your pussy.
クロちゃん、おまんこに注意して
Open it.
開いて
Up to the hole.
穴まで
delicious?
おいしい?
Take more.
もっと取って
Please.
お願いして
Please add more.
もっと付いてください
Does it feel good?
気持ちいい?
black
クロ
Chan, I want to take it out.
ちゃん、 出したいよ
I want to put it out.
出したい
I'll let you take it.
持って行かせてあげるから